[
    {
        "question": "I love you",
        "words": {
          "4": "by",
          "1": "you",
          "3": "love",
          "2": "are",
          "5": "me",
          "6": "loved"
        },
        "answers":[[1,2,6,4,5]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I take the pen",
        "words": {
          "4": "took",
          "1": "me",
          "3": "the",
          "2": "is",
          "5": "me",
          "6": "was",
          "7": "by",
          "8": "pen",
          "9": "taken"
        },
        "answers":[[3,8,2,9,7,5]]
    },
    {
        "question": "We play football",
        "words": {
          "4": "football",
          "1": "we",
          "3": "by",
          "2": "is",
          "5": "us",
          "6": "play",
          "7": "played"
        },
        "answers":[[4,2,7,3,5]]
    },
    {
        "question": "No one hates me",
        "words": {
          "4": "me",
          "1": "I",
          "3": "by",
          "2": "one",
          "5": "do",
          "6": "hated",
          "7": "not",
          "8": "hates",
          "9": "no",
          "10": "am"
        },
        "answers":[[1,10,6,3,9,2]]
    },
    {
        "question": "You do not like them",
        "words": {
          "4": "not",
          "1": "you",
          "3": "by",
          "2": "they",
          "5": "like",
          "6": "do",
          "7": "are",
          "8": "liked",
          "9": "be"
        },
        "answers":[[2,7,4,8,3,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "A dog does not like cats",
        "words": {
          "4": "dog",
          "1": "by",
          "3": "cats",
          "2": "not",
          "5": "be",
          "6": "liked",
          "7": "are",
          "8": "a",
          "9": "like",
          "10": "do"
        },
        "answers":[[3,7,2,6,1,8,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pinky laughs loudly",
        "words": {
          "4": "Pinky",
          "1": "by",
          "3": "loudly",
          "2": "is",
          "5": "laughed"
        },
        "answers":[[]]
    },
    {
        "question": "He is a liar",
        "words": {
          "4": "he",
          "1": "a",
          "3": "him",
          "2": "by",
          "5": "liar",
          "6": "being"
        },
        "answers":[[]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I am doing yoga now",
        "words": {
          "4": "Yoga",
          "1": "now",
          "3": "been",
          "2": "by",
          "5": "doing",
          "6": "being",
          "7": "me",
          "8": "done"
        },
        "answers":[[4,9,6,8,2,7,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "My mother is giving me food",
        "words": {
          "4": "food",
          "1": "been",
          "3": "mother",
          "2": "I",
          "5": "my",
          "6": "given",
          "7": "am",
          "8": "by",
          "9": "is",
          "10": "being",
          "11": "me"
        },
        "answers":[[2,7,10,6,4,8,5,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Your music has made a painful sound",
        "words": {
          "4": "music",
          "1": "is",
          "3": "sound",
          "2": "your",
          "5": "a",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "been",
          "8": "having",
          "9": "painful",
          "10": "has",
          "11": "made",
          "12": "had"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,3,10,7,11,6,2,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mr. Mitra had taught us grammar",
        "words": {
          "4": "Mr. Mitra",
          "1": "had",
          "3": "grammar",
          "2": "we",
          "5": "by",
          "6": "been",
          "7": "to",
          "8": "the",
          "9": "us",
          "10": "taught",
          "11": ""
        },
        "answers":[[2,1,6,10,3,5,4]]
    }
]